<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<content connectType="Marketo" sourceType="Email" sourceName="Blank _TetsR" sourceId="2557">
    <field id="2557" name="subject" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[chêéck thêé RJáåpáån-Têést191]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_1" name="html" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[<p>Bûùmræåh&rsquo;s lâåst twõó õóvéérs yïïééldééd õónly fïïvéé rùüns, âånd mùüch âås Éõóïïn Mõórgâån mâåy fùüméé âåbõóùüt théé ùümpïïrïïng &mdash; hëê håæs åæ póôíînt &mdash; théêréê íís nôó déênyííng thæát Ènglæánd lôóôókéêd clüüéêléêss æágæáíínst théê Güüjæáræát bôówléêr&rsquo;s áâssöòrtmèént öòf yöòrkèérs áând öòff-cùùttèérs.<br />Nêëhrãâ hãâs lòõst lïïttlêë òõf hïïs còõmpêëtïïtïïvêë fïïrêë; ãâny lãâck òõf spêëêëd òõn thêë fïïêëld (thêërêë wãâs ãân òõccãâsïïòõn ïïn Nãâgpùúr whêën òõnêë còõmmêëntãâtòõr rêëmãârkêëd òõn ãâïïr thãât thêë 37-yêëãâr-òõld wãâs &ldquo;éèscôörtìíng théè bæãll tôö théè bôöúýndæãry&rdquo;) íïs cöõmpèènsäâtèèd föõr wíïth èèxpèèríïèèncèè äând böõwlíïng skíïll.<br />Úp ùüntíîl thêè clòösíîng ståägêès åät thêè VCÂ Ståädíîùüm, thòöùügh, thêè víîsíîtòör&rsquo;s böõwléèrs häád öõùütshöõnéè théèïìr cöõùüntéèrpäárts ïìn théè T20s.<br />Chrïîs Jõôrdæân, whõô æâppêêæârs tõô êênjõôy õôpêêræâtïîng æât thêê dêêæâth, æând Tymæâl Mïîlls hæâvêê hïît thêê rïîght lêêngths ïîn thêê twõô gæâmêês, æând úúsêêd thêêïîr slõôwêêr dêêlïîvêêrïîêês tõô grêêæât êêffêêct. Mòóèêèên Ålîï, mèêâãnwhîïlèê, hâãs fîïgýürèês òóf thrèêèê fòór 41 fròóm hîïs èêîïght òóvèêrs.</p>]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_1" name="text" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[Bûùmrãàh’s lãàst twòô òôvèérs yïïèéldèéd òônly fïïvèé rûùns, ãànd mûùch ãàs Ëòôïïn Mòôrgãàn mãày fûùmèé ãàbòôûùt thèé ûùmpïïrïïng — hèé hãàs ãà pòôïïnt — thèérèé ïïs nòô dèényïïng thãàt Ënglãànd lòôòôkèéd clûùèélèéss ãàgãàïïnst thèé Gûùjãàrãàt bòôwlèér’s ãàssòôrtmèént òôf yòôrkèérs ãànd òôff-cûùttèérs. Néèhráå háås lóóst lïíttléè óóf hïís cóómpéètïítïívéè fïíréè; áåny láåck óóf spéèéèd óón théè fïíéèld (théèréè wáås áån óóccáåsïíóón ïín Náågpýùr whéèn óónéè cóómméèntáåtóór réèmáårkéèd óón áåïír tháåt théè 37-yéèáår-óóld wáås “éèscóórtïíng théè báåll tóó théè bóóýùndáåry”) ïís cóómpéènsáåtéèd fóór wïíth éèxpéèrïíéèncéè áånd bóówlïíng skïíll. Úp ûüntíìl thëê clóósíìng stäâgëês äât thëê VCÆ Stäâdíìûüm, thóóûügh, thëê víìsíìtóór’s bóówlëêrs häâd óóûütshóónëê thëêíìr cóóûüntëêrpäârts íìn thëê T20s. Chrîïs Jóördàæn, whóö àæppêèàærs tóö êènjóöy óöpêèràætîïng àæt thêè dêèàæth, àænd Tymàæl Mîïlls hàævêè hîït thêè rîïght lêèngths îïn thêè twóö gàæmêès, àænd ûùsêèd thêèîïr slóöwêèr dêèlîïvêèrîïêès tóö grêèàæt êèffêèct. Môöéééén Ãlïí, mééâânwhïíléé, hââs fïígùùréés ôöf thréééé fôör 41 frôöm hïís ééïíght ôövéérs.]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_2" name="html" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[<p>Ïndîìãâ&rsquo;s bæætsmêên wììll hòópêê fòór grêêæætêêr süüccêêss æægææììnst thêêm, òón ææ süürfææcêê thææt ììs lììkêêly tòó bêê mòórêê ææmêênææblêê tòó rüün-mæækììng thææn thêê òónêê thêêy lææst êêncòóüüntêêrêêd.<br />Thêë KSCÂ cýüräãtóôr, K. Srîìräãm, häãs säãîìd hêë êëxpêëcts scóôrêës îìn thêë rêëgîìóôn óôf 170; thêë sîìzêë óôf thêë gróôýünd (wîìth îìts îìmmäãcýüläãtêëly lýüsh óôýütfîìêëld, thäãnks tóô äã nêëw väãcýüýüm-póôwêërêëd dräãîìnäãgêë systêëm) wîìll äãlsóô hêëlp îìn thîìs rêëgäãrd.<br />Ít ìïs äâ rëëlìïëëf tõö Índìïäâ thäât K.L. Räâhüúl häâs fõöüúnd fõörm äât thëë tõöp õöf thëë õördëër. Thëê Kæærnæætæækææ bæætsmææn hææd mæædëê scóörëês óöf 8, 5, 11, æænd 8 lëêæædííng ûýp tóö híís swææshbûýcklííng 71 óön Sûýndææy.<br />Héê îìs àànóóthéêr óóf thóóséê whóó féêààtüüréêd héêréê îìn théê ÌPL fîìnààl lààst Màày (Jóórdààn, Yüüzvéêndràà Chààhààl, àànd Bhüüvnéêshwààr Küümààr théê réêst), théê éênd óóf àà tóóüürnààméênt thààt sààw hîìm déêstróóy ààny nóótîìóón thààt héê wààs àà plààyéêr üünsüüîìtéêd tóó lîìmîìtéêd-óóvéêrs crîìckéêt.</p>]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_2" name="text" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[Îndìîäá’s bäátsmëën wìîll hõôpëë fõôr grëëäátëër süùccëëss äágäáìînst thëëm, õôn äá süùrfäácëë thäát ìîs lìîkëëly tõô bëë mõôrëë äámëënäáblëë tõô rüùn-mäákìîng thäán thëë õônëë thëëy läást ëëncõôüùntëërëëd. Thèê KSCÅ cýûráätôòr, K. Sríïráäm, háäs sáäíïd hèê èêxpèêcts scôòrèês íïn thèê rèêgíïôòn ôòf 170; thèê síïzèê ôòf thèê grôòýûnd (wíïth íïts íïmmáäcýûláätèêly lýûsh ôòýûtfíïèêld, tháänks tôò áä nèêw váäcýûýûm-pôòwèêrèêd dráäíïnáägèê systèêm) wíïll áälsôò hèêlp íïn thíïs rèêgáärd. Ït ïïs áà rèêlïïèêf töô Ïndïïáà tháàt K.L. Ráàhùùl háàs föôùùnd föôrm áàt thèê töôp öôf thèê öôrdèêr. Théè Káàrnáàtáàkáà báàtsmáàn háàd máàdéè scõóréès õóf 8, 5, 11, áànd 8 léèáàdïìng ûýp tõó hïìs swáàshbûýcklïìng 71 õón Sûýndáày. Hêë ìís áånôöthêër ôöf thôösêë whôö fêëáåtûýrêëd hêërêë ìín thêë ÌPL fìínáål láåst Máåy (Jôördáån, Yûýzvêëndráå Cháåháål, áånd Bhûývnêëshwáår Kûýmáår thêë rêëst), thêë êënd ôöf áå tôöûýrnáåmêënt tháåt sáåw hìím dêëstrôöy áåny nôötìíôön tháåt hêë wáås áå pláåyêër ûýnsûýìítêëd tôö lìímìítêëd-ôövêërs crìíckêët.]]></field>
</content>
