<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<content connectType="Marketo" sourceType="Email" sourceName="Blank _TetsR" sourceId="2557">
    <field id="2557" name="subject" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[chééck théé RJææpææn-Téést191]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_1" name="html" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[<p>Bùümrááh&rsquo;s lãâst twõò õòvèërs yïìèëldèëd õònly fïìvèë rýúns, ãând mýúch ãâs Èõòïìn Mõòrgãân mãây fýúmèë ãâbõòýút thèë ýúmpïìrïìng &mdash; hêé hâæs âæ pöõîìnt &mdash; thêêrêê îís nõò dêênyîíng thåät Ênglåänd lõòõòkêêd clúûêêlêêss åägåäîínst thêê Gúûjåäråät bõòwlêêr&rsquo;s áãssõòrtmêènt õòf yõòrkêèrs áãnd õòff-cùüttêèrs.<br />Néêhrãà hãàs lòöst lïïttléê òöf hïïs còömpéêtïïtïïvéê fïïréê; ãàny lãàck òöf spéêéêd òön théê fïïéêld (théêréê wãàs ãàn òöccãàsïïòön ïïn Nãàgpüûr whéên òönéê còömméêntãàtòör réêmãàrkéêd òön ãàïïr thãàt théê 37-yéêãàr-òöld wãàs &ldquo;êêscóórtïìng thêê bååll tóó thêê bóóúúndååry&rdquo;) íís cóõmpëénsæãtëéd fóõr wííth ëéxpëérííëéncëé æãnd bóõwlííng skííll.<br />Ûp ùýntïïl thëè clôósïïng stáágëès áát thëè VCÀ Stáádïïùým, thôóùýgh, thëè vïïsïïtôór&rsquo;s böówlêèrs hâäd öóúütshöónêè thêèìír cöóúüntêèrpâärts ìín thêè T20s.<br />Chríìs Jöòrdæän, whöò æäppèéæärs töò èénjöòy öòpèéræätíìng æät thèé dèéæäth, æänd Tymæäl Míìlls hæävèé híìt thèé ríìght lèéngths íìn thèé twöò gæämèés, æänd ùýsèéd thèéíìr slöòwèér dèélíìvèéríìèés töò grèéæät èéffèéct. Mòõëèëèn Ãlïï, mëèãænwhïïlëè, hãæs fïïgýürëès òõf thrëèëè fòõr 41 fròõm hïïs ëèïïght òõvëèrs.</p>]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_1" name="text" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[Bùýmrääh’s lääst twóó óóvëërs yïïëëldëëd óónly fïïvëë rùýns, äänd mùých ääs Êóóïïn Móórgään määy fùýmëë ääbóóùýt thëë ùýmpïïrïïng — hëë hääs ää póóïïnt — thëërëë ïïs nóó dëënyïïng thäät Êngläänd lóóóókëëd clùýëëlëëss äägääïïnst thëë Gùýjääräät bóówlëër’s äässóórtmëënt óóf yóórkëërs äänd óóff-cùýttëërs. Nëéhræä hæäs lóõst lîìttlëé óõf hîìs cóõmpëétîìtîìvëé fîìrëé; æäny læäck óõf spëéëéd óõn thëé fîìëéld (thëérëé wæäs æän óõccæäsîìóõn îìn Næägpûùr whëén óõnëé cóõmmëéntæätóõr rëémæärkëéd óõn æäîìr thæät thëé 37-yëéæär-óõld wæäs “ëéscóõrtîìng thëé bæäll tóõ thëé bóõûùndæäry”) îìs cóõmpëénsæätëéd fóõr wîìth ëéxpëérîìëéncëé æänd bóõwlîìng skîìll. Üp üýntíìl thèè clôòsíìng stââgèès âât thèè VCÂ Stââdíìüým, thôòüýgh, thèè víìsíìtôòr’s bôòwlèèrs hââd ôòüýtshôònèè thèèíìr côòüýntèèrpâârts íìn thèè T20s. Chríìs Jôòrdâän, whôò âäppéëâärs tôò éënjôòy ôòpéërâätíìng âät théë déëâäth, âänd Tymâäl Míìlls hâävéë híìt théë ríìght léëngths íìn théë twôò gâäméës, âänd ûûséëd théëíìr slôòwéër déëlíìvéëríìéës tôò gréëâät éëfféëct. Môõêèêèn Älìî, mêèâãnwhìîlêè, hâãs fìîgùûrêès ôõf thrêèêè fôõr 41 frôõm hìîs êèìîght ôõvêèrs.]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_2" name="html" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[<p>Ìndíïâä&rsquo;s báâtsmèën wîíll hõópèë fõór grèëáâtèër süúccèëss áâgáâîínst thèëm, õón áâ süúrfáâcèë tháât îís lîíkèëly tõó bèë mõórèë áâmèënáâblèë tõó rüún-máâkîíng tháân thèë õónèë thèëy láâst èëncõóüúntèërèëd.<br />Thèé KSCÅ cúùråátôòr, K. Srîîråám, håás såáîîd hèé èéxpèécts scôòrèés îîn thèé rèégîîôòn ôòf 170; thèé sîîzèé ôòf thèé grôòúùnd (wîîth îîts îîmmåácúùlåátèély lúùsh ôòúùtfîîèéld, thåánks tôò åá nèéw våácúùúùm-pôòwèérèéd dråáîînåágèé systèém) wîîll åálsôò hèélp îîn thîîs rèégåárd.<br />Ît ìís æà rëèlìíëèf tõô Îndìíæà thæàt K.L. Ræàhúùl hæàs fõôúùnd fõôrm æàt thëè tõôp õôf thëè õôrdëèr. Théé Käàrnäàtäàkäà bäàtsmäàn häàd mäàdéé scóóréés óóf 8, 5, 11, äànd 8 lééäàdììng ùûp tóó hììs swäàshbùûcklììng 71 óón Sùûndäày.<br />Hèè íís ãânööthèèr ööf thöösèè whöö fèèãâtùúrèèd hèèrèè íín thèè ÎPL fíínãâl lãâst Mãây (Jöördãân, Yùúzvèèndrãâ Chãâhãâl, ãând Bhùúvnèèshwãâr Kùúmãâr thèè rèèst), thèè èènd ööf ãâ tööùúrnãâmèènt thãât sãâw híím dèèströöy ãâny nöötííöön thãât hèè wãâs ãâ plãâyèèr ùúnsùúíítèèd töö líímíítèèd-öövèèrs crííckèèt.</p>]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_2" name="text" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[Ìndííåá’s båátsmêên wííll hóöpêê fóör grêêåátêêr sùýccêêss åágåáíínst thêêm, óön åá sùýrfåácêê thåát íís lííkêêly tóö bêê móörêê åámêênåáblêê tóö rùýn-måákííng thåán thêê óönêê thêêy låást êêncóöùýntêêrêêd. Théé KSCÅ cúúráátòôr, K. Srìîráám, háás sááìîd héé ééxpéécts scòôréés ìîn théé réégìîòôn òôf 170; théé sìîzéé òôf théé gròôúúnd (wìîth ìîts ìîmmáácúúláátéély lúúsh òôúútfìîééld, tháánks tòô áá nééw váácúúúúm-pòôwéérééd drááìînáágéé systéém) wìîll áálsòô héélp ìîn thìîs réégáárd. Ìt ïîs ãà rèêlïîèêf tòô Ìndïîãà thãàt K.L. Rãàhûýl hãàs fòôûýnd fòôrm ãàt thèê tòôp òôf thèê òôrdèêr. Thèè Kåårnååtååkåå bååtsmåån hååd måådèè scôôrèès ôôf 8, 5, 11, åånd 8 lèèåådïìng üýp tôô hïìs swååshbüýcklïìng 71 ôôn Süýndååy. Hèê íïs áänòõthèêr òõf thòõsèê whòõ fèêáätùúrèêd hèêrèê íïn thèê ÎPL fíïnáäl láäst Máäy (Jòõrdáän, Yùúzvèêndráä Cháäháäl, áänd Bhùúvnèêshwáär Kùúmáär thèê rèêst), thèê èênd òõf áä tòõùúrnáämèênt tháät sáäw híïm dèêstròõy áäny nòõtíïòõn tháät hèê wáäs áä pláäyèêr ùúnsùúíïtèêd tòõ líïmíïtèêd-òõvèêrs críïckèêt.]]></field>
</content>
