<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<content connectType="Marketo" sourceType="Email" sourceName="Blank _TetsR" sourceId="2557">
    <field id="2557" name="subject" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[check the RJapan-Test191]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_1" name="html" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[<p>Bumrah&rsquo;s last two overs yielded only five runs, and much as Eoin Morgan may fume about the umpiring &mdash; he has a point &mdash; there is no denying that England looked clueless against the Gujarat bowler&rsquo;s assortment of yorkers and off-cutters.<br />Nehra has lost little of his competitive fire; any lack of speed on the field (there was an occasion in Nagpur when one commentator remarked on air that the 37-year-old was &ldquo;escorting the ball to the boundary&rdquo;) is compensated for with experience and bowling skill.<br />Up until the closing stages at the VCA Stadium, though, the visitor&rsquo;s bowlers had outshone their counterparts in the T20s.<br />Chris Jordan, who appears to enjoy operating at the death, and Tymal Mills have hit the right lengths in the two games, and used their slower deliveries to great effect. Moeen Ali, meanwhile, has figures of three for 41 from his eight overs.</p>]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_1" name="text" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[Bumrah’s last two overs yielded only five runs, and much as Eoin Morgan may fume about the umpiring — he has a point — there is no denying that England looked clueless against the Gujarat bowler’s assortment of yorkers and off-cutters.
Nehra has lost little of his competitive fire; any lack of speed on the field (there was an occasion in Nagpur when one commentator remarked on air that the 37-year-old was “escorting the ball to the boundary”) is compensated for with experience and bowling skill.
Up until the closing stages at the VCA Stadium, though, the visitor’s bowlers had outshone their counterparts in the T20s.
Chris Jordan, who appears to enjoy operating at the death, and Tymal Mills have hit the right lengths in the two games, and used their slower deliveries to great effect. Moeen Ali, meanwhile, has figures of three for 41 from his eight overs.]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_2" name="html" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[<p>India&rsquo;s batsmen will hope for greater success against them, on a surface that is likely to be more amenable to run-making than the one they last encountered.<br />The KSCA curator, K. Sriram, has said he expects scores in the region of 170; the size of the ground (with its immaculately lush outfield, thanks to a new vacuum-powered drainage system) will also help in this regard.<br />It is a relief to India that K.L. Rahul has found form at the top of the order. The Karnataka batsman had made scores of 8, 5, 11, and 8 leading up to his swashbuckling 71 on Sunday.<br />He is another of those who featured here in the IPL final last May (Jordan, Yuzvendra Chahal, and Bhuvneshwar Kumar the rest), the end of a tournament that saw him destroy any notion that he was a player unsuited to limited-overs cricket.</p>]]></field>
    <field id="edit_text_2" name="text" translate="true" maxLength="0" metadata="false"><![CDATA[India’s batsmen will hope for greater success against them, on a surface that is likely to be more amenable to run-making than the one they last encountered.
The KSCA curator, K. Sriram, has said he expects scores in the region of 170; the size of the ground (with its immaculately lush outfield, thanks to a new vacuum-powered drainage system) will also help in this regard.
It is a relief to India that K.L. Rahul has found form at the top of the order. The Karnataka batsman had made scores of 8, 5, 11, and 8 leading up to his swashbuckling 71 on Sunday.
He is another of those who featured here in the IPL final last May (Jordan, Yuzvendra Chahal, and Bhuvneshwar Kumar the rest), the end of a tournament that saw him destroy any notion that he was a player unsuited to limited-overs cricket.]]></field>
</content>
